{
    "id": "fab898787c5548159a0387a309ab44d5",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don’t think that I ………………….. be able to come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dcd4a9b7ac38472687b3836777dc9c9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… not pay unless he is compelled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "will",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c355549a316c499d9489210c3e471771"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ..................... be punctual.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "ought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4277930d1a85493f9cfcdbd3704f786d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ………………….tell me earlier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a1c8909d019347dda5102d238d9d5faf"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… I help you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Shall",
                "Will",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2f3284d110174792a906a1dcbc3fa4e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you help me with this, please?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Shall",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a7c6942720bd4a22a7fd45ec9bcfe515"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said I ………………….. visit him at any time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b26a422710c407ea73d83dee705be55"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ………………… see her, give her my love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1d0723875f8428bb9e07b5614a0f672"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. not ask for a raise for fear of losing his job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dare",
                "need",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54a5a15038b842febef53344b50b58be"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. him, so I phoned him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "needn't to see",
                "didn't need to see",
                "needn't have seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "77cb16df424241afb04b5463f7044433"
        }
    ]
}